Guide to the Yale University Divinity School Memorabilia Collection
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Audio-Visual Materials, Series V; *NOTE: CDs of Convocation lectures are available for purchase from the Yale Divinity School Bookstore (http://www.yaledivinitybookstore.com/category/audio-and-lectures)
  - Audio
    - Panels/ Conferences/ Discussions
      - Visiting Lecturers and Miscellaneous Recordings
        - Jones, Clinton: "Human Sexuality and Ethics" (Tape), 1972 (Box 97)
        - Chapel Echoes (audio reel), 1974 May 24 (Box 96)
        - Reuther, Rosemary: "Romanticism, the Cult of True Womanhood as a Critique of Industrial Society" (Tape), 1974 (Box 94)
        - Hooper, Fr. Walter: "A True, Good, Patient, Man" (Tape), 1975 Sep 18 (Box 94)
        - Luther's Deutsche Messe, Performed by Institute of Sacred Music, YDS Capella Choir (2 Audio Reels), 1975 Oct 15 (Box 96)
        - Dyer, Rev. Mark J: "Spiritual Leadership in the Local Congregation" (Tape), 1976 Oct 22 (Box 94)
        - Brown, Robert M: "Liberation in a Global Context" (CD/Tape), 1977 (Box 94)
        - Knox, David Walter: "Heaven and Hell in Historical Perspective" (Tape), 1977 (Box 94)
        - Muzorewa, Bishop Abel Tendekai: "The Chruch in Rhodesia" (Tape), 1977 Apr 22 (Box 94)
        - Marty, Martin: "From the Inward Seventies to the Outward Eighties" (2CDs/Tapes), 1979 (Box 94)
        - Fairweather, Eugene: "An Anglican Commentator" (3CDs/Tapes), 1980 (Box 94)
        - Gerrish, Brian: "The Reformation Reassessed" (CD/Tape), 1980 (Box 94)
        - Weigle, Richard: "Opening Convocation Address", 1980 Sep 4 (Box 106)
        - Christ, Carol: "God and Goddess in Feminist Theology" (Tape), 1981 (Box 97)
        - Gottwald, Norman: "The Theological Task After The Twelve Tribe of Yahweh " (Tape), 1981 (Box 97)
        - Plaskow, Judith: "Woman as Body: Motherhood and Dualism" (Tape), 1981 (Box 97)
        - Hart, Sen. Gary: "Toward Replacing Economics", 1982 Sep 8 (Box 97)
        - Dunston, Bishop A.G: "The Rise of the Black Chruch" (Tape), 1983 Oct 6 (Box 97)
        - Gettier, John A: "God and Evil in the Bible" (Tape), 1983 (Box 97)
        - Kirkpatrick, Frank: "The Bible, The Bishops, and the Bomb" (Tape), 1983 (Box 103)
        - Ozmert, Steven: "Reformation as Intellectual Revolution" (Tape), 1983 (Box 97)
        - Pannenberg, W: "Yale Address " (CD/Tape), 1983 (Box 97)
        - Baum, Gregory: "The Return of the Social Gospel in the Christian Church" (4 CDs/3 Tapes), 1984 (Box 97)
        - Hoyt, Tom: "Theological Education and the Black Ministries" (Tape), 1984 Feb 21 (Box 97)
        - Westerfield, Bradford H: "Is the Cold War Inescapable?" Dwight Chapel Adult Education Series (Tape), 1984 Feb 26 (Box 97)
        - Tutu, Desmond: "The Witness of a Contemporary Christian" (3 CDs/2Tapes), 1984 Oct 23 (Box 98)
        - Berrigan, Daniel "Is the Peace Movement Still Moving?" (CD/Tape), 1985 (Box 98)
        - Coffin, W.S: "Keeping Peace and Justice Together" (CD/Tape), 1985 (Box 98)
        - Walls, Andrew: "Africa and the Future of the Christian Faith" (Tape), 1985 Sep 24 (Box 98)
        - Mayson, Cedric: "Faith, Oppression and South Africa; The Liberation of South Africa" (2 Tapes), 1986 (Box 98)
        - McCormick, R: "The Gift of Life: Medical Technology and Morality" (2 Tapes), 1987 (Box 98)
        - Mead, Rev. Loren B: "Conversation" (Tape), 1987 (Box 98)
        - Post, Avery: "Conversations" (Tape), 1987 (Box 98)
        - Rosazza, Bishop Peter: "Conversations"(Tape), 1987 Jun 4 (Box 98)
        - Reuther, Rosemary: "Feminist Theology" (Tape), 1987 (Box 98)
        - Burguss, (Bishop): "Epsicopal Reflections on Ministry and on Racial Issues Facing the Church" (Tape), 1987 Nov 2 (Box 98)
        - Smith, John: "On Recent Trends in Philosophy" (Tape), 1987 (Box 98)
        - Spong, John Shelby: "Report on the Task Force in Changing Patterns of Sexuality and Family Life" (CD/Tape), 1987 (Box 99)
        - Tracey, David: "Work in Progress" (Tape), 1987 (Box 99)
        - Adams, Robert: "Leture" (CD/Tape), 1988 (Box 99)
        - Anderson, Bernard: "Lecture" (Tape), 1988 (Box 73)
        - Kafity, Rt Rev: "On the Middle East as Lived by a Palestinian Arab Christian Bishop in Jerusalem" (Tape), 1988 Feb 2 (Box 99)
        - Higgins, George: "What's New in Human Sexuality Research" (Tape), 1988 (Box 99)
        - Higgins, George: "Normality and Morality in Human Sexuality" (Tape), 1988 (Box 99)
        - Jones, Rev. Alan W: "Spirituality and Secular Humanism" (CD/Tape), 1988 Jun 12 (Box 99)
        - Bartlett, David: "Children in Worship: Children and Preaching", 1992 (Box 99a)
        - Wright, Jeremiah: Luccock Visitorship (Tape), 1992-1993 (Box 99)
        - May, William F "Inauguaral Convocation Lecture", 1995 Oct 9 (Box 99)
        - Evensong (Tape), 1995 Oct 12 (Box 99)
        - Plantinga-Pauw, Amy: "Jonathan Edwards: Theologian of Divine Eminence", 2003 Oct 10 (Box 106)
        - Meeks, Wyane: "Inventing the Christ: Multicultural Process and Poetry Among the First Christians", 2003 Nov 18 (Box 106)
        - Oduyoye, Mercy: lecture in Latourette Hall, 2004 Jan 22 (Box 106)
        - "About Abortion", n.d. (Box 99)
        - Allen, David F: "Religion and Psychology" (Tape) (Box 99)
        - Baillie, John: "They Have Their Reward" (Tape), n.d. (Box 99)
        - Batchelor, John Calvin: "Antiutopia and Tomorrow's News: The Birth of the People's Republic of Antarctica" (CD/Tape) (Box 100)
        - Bethge, Eberhard: "Friend and Biographer of Dietrich Bonhoeffer" (CD/Tape) (Box 100)
        - Cornell, Tom - Director of Waterbury Area Council of Churches: "Minister as Counselor" (Tape), n.d. (Box 97)
        - Crane, Henry: "The Evangelism of Emphasis" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 75)
        - Dulles, Avery: "The Catholicity of Augsburg Confession / The Reformation Reassessed" (Tape), n.d. (Box 100)
        - Fishbane, Michael: "Buber and the Bible" (Tape) (Box 100)
        - Fishbane: "Religion and Religiosity in the Thought of Buber" (Tape) (Box 100)
        - Fosdick: "My Field is the World: Charles Brown on Dwight L. Moody" (CD/Tape) (Box 100)
        - Gibbs, Mark: "The Future of Christianity: The Vision of William Temple" (Tape), n.d. (Box 100)
        - Gilkey, Langdon: "Lectue" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 101)
        - Gilkey: "Present Problems in Theology" (Tape), n.d. (Box 101)
        - Green, Michael: "The Church God Looks For"; "The Church of the Servant"; "Spiritual Warfare"; "The Church - Full of Ministers" (4 Tapes), n.d. (Box 100)
        - Gonzales, Catherine and Justo: "Women and Human Liberation" Women's Interseminary Conference (Tape) (Box 102)
        - Gustafson, James M: "Christ and Culture: An Appreciative Interpretation" Dedication of Niebuhr Hall (Tape) (Box 102)
        - Gustafson: "Ethics and Experimentation: A Procedural Approach" (Tape) (Box 102)
        - Frei, Hans: "Response to Carl F.H. Henry's Lecture: ' Narrative Theology: An Evangelical View'" (Tape), n.d. (Box 102)
        - Hargrove, Barbara: "The Role of the Family in an Era of Social Change", n.d. (Box 106)
        - Hart, Sr. Joan,Peace Educator for the Archdiocese of N.Y :"Minister as Teacher" (Tape), n.d. (Box 102)
        - Henry, Carl F. H.: "The Crisis of Biblical Authority" Reponse by Richard Hays (Tape), n.d. (Box 77)
        - Henry: "Narrative Theology: An Evangelical View" Response by Hans Frei (Tape), n.d. (Box 102)
        - Henry: "On Divine Revelation" Response by Paul Homer (Box 102)
        - Hurd, David: " Singing in the Liturgy"; "Psalmody in the Liturgy"; "Hymns in the Liturgy"; "Ministry Through the Music Parish" (6 CDs/Tapes), n.d. (Box 102)
        - Iasi-Diaz, Ada Maria: "Sisterhood: Core of Liberating Struggle" (CD/Tape), n.d. (Box 102)
        - Illich, Ivan: "The End of Schooling" (Tape) (Box 103)
        - Jakubowska-Pluzanska, Dr. Janina: "Marxism and Christianity in Contemporary Poland" (Tape) (Box 103)
        - Johnson, Zigler, and Como: "Reflections" - Gays and Lesbians in the Ministry Forum (Tape 2 only) (Box 103)
        - King, Martin Luther: "Sermon on Peace" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 101)
        - Kirkpatrick, Frank: "Contemporary Theology in the United States" (CD/Tape), n.d. (Box 103)
        - Kirkpatrick, Frank: "Moral Issues in Business and the Economic Order" (Tape) (Box 103)
        - Kung, Hans: "To What We Still Can Cling" (3 CDs/2 Tapes), n.d. (Box 103)
        - Littel, Franklin: "The Significance of the Holocuast for Christians" (Tape), n.d. (Box 103)
        - McBrian, Richard: "The Mission and Ministry of the Church" (Tape) (Box 103)
        - Melchert, Charles: "The Future of Religious Education" (Tape), n.d. (Box 103)
        - Miller, Jean Baker: "Toward a New Psycology of Women" (Tape), n.d. (Box 103)
        - Mitchell, Henry: "The Genius of the Black Pulpit" (4 Tapes), n.d. (Box 90)
        - Morrison, Bruce, Congressman: "Service and Vision" (Tape) (Box 103)
        - Neill, Stephen: "Christian Ideals and Indian National Progress" (Tape) (Box 103)
        - Newbigin, Lesslie: "The Lord High and Lifted Up" (Tape) (Box 103)
        - Niebuhr, Reinhold: "Faith, Hope, and Love I Cor. 13" (Audio Reel) (Box 101)
        - Niebuhr: " Mattew 5:44" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 75)
        - Niebuhr: "Lecture" (6 Audio Reels), n.d. (Box 101)
        - Peale, Norman Vincent (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 101)
        - Pennington, Fr. Basil: "Prayer" (Tape), n.d. (Box 106)
        - Potok (2 Audio Reels), n.d. (Box 101)
        - Randall, Claire: "Women in the Church" (Tape) (Box 100)
        - Richardson, Nevilla: "Being the Church in South Africa" (Tape), n.d. (Box 105)
        - Saliers, Don: "Theology, Worship, Emotion" (Tape), n.d. (Box 105)
        - Schaef, Ann Wilson: "Exploration of the Male-Female System" (2 Tapes), n.d. (Box 105)
        - Schaef: "A Theortical-Conceptual Framework for Women's Therapy" (2 Tapes), n.d. (Box 105)
        - Schantz, Mark: Guitar Music (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 101)
        - Schillebeeckx, Fr. Edward: "Contemporary Experience and Religious Phenomenon; Authority and Contemporary Experience; God Within the Context of Liberation" (4 CDs/3Tapes) (Box 105)
        - Sheen, (Bishop) (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 104)
        - Shoemaker (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 104)
        - Soelle, Dorothea: "Theological Tools--Liberation" (Tape), n.d. (Box 106)
        - Stendahl, Krister: "The Jewishness of Jesus and his Gentile Followers" (Tape) (Box 106)
        - Thielecke, H: "Lecture" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 104)
        - Tillich, Paul: "Be Not Conformed" (CD/Tape), n.d. (Box 105)
        - Vickers, Nancy: "The Renassiance Utopia and Montaigne's 'Les Cannibals'" (CD/Tape) (Box 105)
        - Weatherhead, Rev. L: "Lecture" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 95)
        - Weicker: "Political Ethics" (Tape), n.d. (Box 106)
      - Discussion/Forums 1970s
        - Panel Discussion - B.R. Skinner, Rollo May Blanchard, Paul Ricoeur- Chaired by Jarislav Pelikan (Audio Reel), 1972 Apr 19 (Box 86)
        - Sexuality Forum: "Divorce" - Lucia Ewing, et. al (Tape), 1975 (Box 86)
        - Sexuality Forum: "Marriage" - Chuck and Libby Powers (CD/Tape), 1975 (Box 86)
        - "History of Women at YDS" - Bainton, Forsberg, Farley, Watson (2 Tapes), 1976 (Box 86)
        - "Homosexuality: Problematic Practice or Legitimate Lifestyle" - J. Dittes, W. Muel, M. Farley (Tape), 1978 (Box 86)
      - 1981 Spirituality Forum
        - Drake, Richard: "Transcendence: The Common Ground for Literary and Theological Discourse" (Tape 2 of 5), 1981 (Box 86)
        - Dupre, Louis: "Spiritual Life in a Secular Age" Spiritual Life Conference (CD/Tape 1 of 5), 1981 (Box 86)
        - La Motte: "The Name in the Stone: Toward a Science of Consciousness" (CD/Tape 3 of 5), 1981 (Box 86)
        - Nouwen, Henri: "The Spiritual Life: A Christian Perspective" (CD/Tape 4 of 5), 1981 (Box 86)
      - Jerusalem: City and Symbol, 1983 YDS Religion and The Arts Program
        - Jerusalem symposium poster, 1983
        - Burrell, David: "The Christian Destiny of Israel (Tape 8), 1983 (Box 90)
        - Kolleck, Teddy: "Jerusalem Today" (Tape 1), 1983 (Box 90)
        - Nohrnberg, James: "Jerusalem Transposed" (Tape 7), 1983 (Box 90)
        - Safide, Moshe: "Stones of Jerusalem" (Tape 5), 1983 (Box 90)
        - Smith, Rodney: "Face to Face in Jerusalem" (Tape 4), 1983 (Box 90)
        - Terrien, Samuel: "Jerusalem in the Bible" (Tape 6), 1983 (Box 90)
      - Peace Making in Ministry Conference, 1984
        - Clark, Rev. Mike: "Minister as Prophet" (Tape), 1984 (Box 97)
        - Cornell, Tom: "Minister as Counselor" (Tape), 1984 (Box 97)
        - Coffin, William Sloanne: "Minister as Preacher" (2 CDs/Tapes), 1984 (Box 97)
        - "Feminist Studies at YDS" - Russell, Copeland, Jones, Garrett, Farley (Tape), 1994 Feb 10 (Box 86)
        - "Theological Discussion: Speaker Lamin Sanneh, Gospel and Culture"; Panel: C. Seitz, B. Childs, R. Fern, L. Keck, K. Greene-McCreight, E. Radner (Tape), 1994 Nov 11 (Box 87)
      - Conference on the Joint Declaration on Justification, 2000
        - Chadwick, Henry (CD/Tape), 2000 (Box 99)
        - Fackre, Gabriel (CD/Tape), 2000 (Box 99)
        - Kasper, Walter (CD/Tape), 2000 (Box 99)
        - Lindbeck, George (CD), 2000 (Box 99)
        - Root, Michael (CD/Tape), 2000 (Box 99)
      - Undated forums/panels
        - "Buber and Christianity" - Leslie Higgins, G. Lindbeck, P. Holmer (Tape) (Box 87)
        - "Ethics Symposium" (Tape 2 of 2), n.d. (Box 87)
        - "Yale Divinity School: Comments and Reflections" (Box 87)
    - Battell Chapel Series/Services
      - "Easter Sunday Morning Service" - William S. Coffin preaching, 1972 Apr 2 (Box 87)
      - "Contemporary Theology: Kierkegaard I" - Paul Holmer (2 Tapes), 1982 Sep 26 (Box 87)
      - "Contemporary Theology: Bultmann" - Wayne Meeks (2 CDs/Tapes), 1982 Oct 17 (Box 87)
      - "Lecture on Christian Unity" - Archbishop Runcie (Tape), 1986 (Box 87)
      - Terry Waite (2 Tapes), 1992 (Box 87)
      - "Miracles" - Paul Holmer (CD/Tape), n.d. (Box 87)
    - Berkeley Divinity School
      - Berkeley Divinity School Convocation/Lectures/Panels
        - "CMS Lectures" - Canon Warren (Audio Reel), 1960 (Box 88)
        - "ISM/Berkeley" - Hicks, Hardy, Minear, Lindbeck (Audio Reel), 1961 (Box 88)
        - "The Christian Ministry: Lay and Ordained"; Panel: Dr. Rodenmayer, W.H. Gray, Dear R.H. Wilmer, Bp. R.H. Stokes,Heywood Fox, William Muehl, Nathan Pusey, Grant Sanger, and Cynthia Wedel (3 CDs/ Audio Reels), 1964 Nov 11 (Box 88)
        - "Spiritual Leadership in the Local Congregation" BDS/YDS Convocation (Tape), 1976 Oct 22 (Box 94)
        - "Into the Regions Beyond" (CD), 2005-2006 (Box 94)
      - Berkeley Divinity School Services
        - Music from Berkeley Divinity School: Morning Prayer; Holy Communion; Evening Prayer; The Litany (Tape, CD), 1960 (Box 90)
        - "A Layman Looks at the Ministry" - de Graffenried (Audio Reel), 1967 Feb10 (Box 89)
        - "Berkeley Association" - Dean Anderson (Audio Reel), 1968 (Box 89)
        - "The Genius of the Black Pulpit" - Henry Mitchell (4 Tapes/CDs), 1974 (Box 90)
        - Blackwood, Andrew: "The Healing of His Seamless Dress" (Audio Reel) (Box 89)
        - Bonnell, J.S: "Preaching and Its Inner Meaning" (Audio Reel) (Box 89)
        - Coffin, Henry S: "Revelation 1:13" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 89)
        - Fisher, The Most Rev. Geoffrey F: "I Peter 4:7" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 89)
        - Graham, William: "Detroit Cru. Hell" (2 Audio Reels), n.d. (Box 91)
        - Graham: "Lecture Untitled" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 91)
        - Graham: "Matthew 7:13" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 91)
        - Kennedy, Gerald: "The Final Triumph" (2 Audio Reels), n.d. (Box 91)
        - Marshall, Peter: "Some Things I Knew" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 91)
        - Marshall, Peter: "Tap on the Shoulder" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 92)
        - Peale, Normen Vincent: "The Art of Successful Wishing" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 92)
        - Newbigin, Lesslie: "The Lord High and Lifted Up" (Audio Reel) (Box 92)
        - Ockenga, Harold: "Following in His Steps" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 92)
        - Pike, James A: "How to Handge Your Past" (Audio Reel) (Box 92)
        - Stewart, James S: "Recapturing the lost Wonder" (Audio Reel) (Box 92)
        - Trueblood, Elton: "Behold Your Calling, Brethren" (Audio Reel), n.d. (Box 92)
        - "An Invitation to Worship at Berkeley Divinity School at Yale: Chapel Sermons 2005-2006"
    - Memorial Services
      - Charles Reynolds Brown (Audio Reel), 1951 (Box 93)
      - Kenneth Latourette (Audio Reel), 1968 Jan 9 (Box 93)
      - Liston Pope, 1974 Apr 23 (Box 93)
      - Robert Watson, 1979 Nov 19 (Box 93)
      - Roland H. Bainton (2 Tapes), 1984 Mar 4 (Box 93)
      - Abraham J. Malherbe (cd), 2012 Oct 27 (Box 93)
    - Marquand Chapel Services
      - Jackson, Jesse: "In the Lion's Den" (Tape), 1974 Mar 5 (Box 90)
      - Hans Kung: "Yale Easter Sermon" (Tape), 1978 (Box 90)
      - Rev. Howard L. Rice, Moderator, UPUSA: Worship Service (Tape), 1980 (Box 90)
      - Ron Krom: "What are You Waiting For" Advent Series (Tape), 1983 (Box 90)
      - Archbishop Demetrius, 2003 Apr 29 (Box 90)
      - Divinity School Choir, directed by James Borden (2 vinyl LPs), 1951/52, 1952/53
    - Yale Divinity School (general)
      - "Yale Divinity School: Comments and Reflections" (audiotape)
    - Duplicate Copies of Tapes/CDs (in LSF)
      - Beecher Lectures, 1949-1979 (Box 111)
      - Beecher Lectures, 1980-1988 (Box 112)
      - Beecher Lectures, 1989-1993 (Box 113)
      - Lectures (arranged alphabetically by last name) A-F (Box 114)
      - Lectures (arranged alphabetically by last name) G-L (Box 115)
      - Lectures (arranged alphabetically by last name) M-W (Box 116)
      - Convocation Lectures / Conferences/ Panels (Box 117)
  - Video
    - Bainton Lectures
      - Miles, Margaret R: "Human Community and Responsibility: Living Beings and Rational Minds in Augustine's Debate with Manicheans", 1995 Oct 10; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995708)
      - Andrew Walls, 2004 Nov 16; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098996300)
    - Bartlett Lectures
      - Michael McGiffert. Religion and Profit Do Jump Together: The First American Pilgrim, 1992 Feb 11; 1 (Box V-13, Item barcode 39002098995328)
      - Nathan Hatch, 1993 Feb 9; 1 (Box V-13, Item barcode 39002098995492)
      - Mark Noll; "The puzzle of Civil War", 1994 Feb 8; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995591)
      - Cahill, Lisa Sowle: "The Family: A Christian Perspective", 1995 Oct 11; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995716)
      - Diane Obenchain, 2004 Nov 9; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098996292)
    - Beecher Lectures
      - Leander Keck, Toward the Renewal of Mainline Protestantism, Lecture 1: "Worship", 1992 Feb 10; 1 (Box V-13, Item barcode 39002098995450)
      - Leander Keck, Toward the Renewal of Mainline Protestantism, Lecture 2: "Theology", 1992 Feb 11; 1 (Box V-13, Item barcode 39002098995468)
      - Leander Keck, Toward the Renewal of Mainline Protestantism, Lecture 3: "Church and Society", 1992 Feb 12; 1 (Box V-13, Item barcode 39002098995476)
      - Leander Keck, Toward the Renewal of Mainline Protestantism, Lecture 4: "Communication", 1992 Feb 13; 1 (Box V-13, Item barcode 39002098995484)
      - Thomas J. Hoyt Jr., Lecture 1: "The Church's Preaching in Pluralistic and Ecumenical Context: Tradition", 1993 Feb 9; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995542)
      - Thomas J. Hoyt Jr., Lecture 3: "Universality: What in the New World Disorder Shall They Preach?", 1993 Feb 11; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995559)
      - Walter Burghardt, Lecture 1: "The Christian Pulpit and Social Justice", 1994 Feb 10; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995609)
      - Walter Burghardt, Lecture 2: "The Christian Pulpit and Social Justice", 1994 Feb 10; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995617)
      - Harry Adams, Lecture 1: "Preaching: The Burden and the Joy", 1995 Oct 9; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995674)
      - Harry Adams, Lecture 2: "Preaching: The Burden and the Joy", 1995 Oct 10; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995682)
      - Harry Adams, Lecture 3: "Preaching: The Burden and the Joy", 1995 Oct 11; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995690)
    - Chisholm Lectures
      - Baruch Levine, 2004 Oct 26; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002129368826)
    - Ensign Lectures
      - William F. May, 1995 Oct 9; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995757)
      - Don Cupitt, 2005 Feb 28; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098996284)
    - Kittel Lectures
      - Susan Niditch, "Oral Culture and Written Documents: Five Attitudes to Writing in the Hebrew Bible", 1994 Apr 20; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995633)
    - Shaffer Lectures
      - Martin Hengel, Lecture 1: "The Historical Jesus: Methods and Sources", 1993 Feb 9; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995567)
      - Martin Hengel, Lecture 2: "Galilean Prophet and Healer", 1993 Feb 10; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995575)
      - Martin Hengel, Lecture 3: "The Crucifed Messiah", 1993 Feb 11; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995583)
    - Sorensen Lecture
      - Beverley Harrison, 1992 Apr 3; 1 (Box V-13, Item barcode 39002098995500)
      - Richard Mollica, 2005 Mar 1; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098996276)
    - Taylor Lectures
      - McFague, Sally, Lecture 1: "Christianity and Postmodern Science", 1994 Feb 9; 1 (Box V-13, Item barcode 39002098995641)
      - McFague, Sallie, Lecture 2: "Christianity and Postmodern Science", 1994 Feb 9; 1 (Box V-13, Item barcode 39002098995658)
      - McFague, Sallie, Lecture 3: "Christianity and Postmodern Science", 1994 Feb 10; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995666)
      - Kaufman, Gordon D., Lecture 1: "Christian Theology in Our Pluralistic World", 1995 Oct 10; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995724)
      - Kaufman, Gordon D., Lecture 2: "Christian Theology in Our Pluralistic World", 1995 Oct 11; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995732)
      - Kaufman, Gordon D., Lecture 3: "Christian Theology in Our Pluralistic World", 1995 Oct 12; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995740)
      - Maurice Wiles, Lecture 1: "Christian Theology Dialogues: Precedents of the Past", 1992 Feb 11; 1 (Box V-13, Item barcode 39002098995518)
      - Maurice Wiles, Lecture 2: "Christian Theology Dialogues: Precedents of the Past", 1992 Feb 11; 1 (Box V-13, Item barcode 39002098995526)
      - Maurice Wiles, Lecture 3: "Christian Theology Dialogues: Precedents of the Past", 1992 Feb 12; 1 (Box V-13, Item barcode 39002098995534)
    - Terry Lectures
      - Dr. David Hartman, Lecture 1; Luce Center Yale University, 1998 Sep 8; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995781)
      - Dr. David Hartman, Lecture 2; Slifka Center; Yale University, 1998 Sep 10; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995765)
      - Dr. David Hartman, Lecture 3; Divinity School; Yale University, 1998 Sep 14 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995773)
    - Other lectures and events
      - ISM Colloquium: Children in the Worshipping Community
        - Experience of Worship; Kyle Pruett, 1992 Mar 4; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002129368792)
        - Children & Music; David Connell, 1992 Mar 25; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002129368800)
        - Children and Preaching; David Bartlett, 1992 Apr 1; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002129368818)
      - Berkeley Divinity School: Admissions video, 1994 Feb 8, n.d.; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995799)
        Convocation Evensong, Lowell Weicker preaching; Admissions video
      - Berkeley winter convocation; Evensong; Lowell Weicker preaching, 1994 Feb; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995617)
      - "Divinity Tomorrow: Supporting Faith and Intellect" (Karyl Evans Productions LLC) (DVD), 2011 May
      - Forum on Theological Inquiry, 1996 Apr 12; 1 (Box V-14, Item barcode 39002098995807)